free-submission-directory.com 2008-12-20

# FS Directory - Privacy policy

When you use our Directory, Free Submission Directory respects and protects your privacy. Information that may specifically identify you as an individual is never collected nor shared with any third parties.

**Information Free Submission Directory DO collect**

Free Submission Directory does not secretly collect information about you, with the exception of providing information during the website submission (standard or premium) , "Take the lead", or banner submission process deliberately. This information is used to contact You to confirm submission or, if there is a need, for a revision of your website or advertisement. When You pay for premium submission, "take the lead", purchasing banner space or donate money to our directory, Free Submission Directory saves information such as date and IP address. This information is used only for security purposes.

**Links to Other (external) websites**

The websites could be displayed as search results or linked by Free Submission Directory through any category which is created by people who are not under Free Submission Directory control. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you read their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Free Submission Directory may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Such changes will be posted on this page.
